Hello, world!
こんにちは、世界！
This is a sample VTT file.
これはサンプルのVTTファイルです。
This file contains 50 subtitles.
このファイルには50個の字幕が含まれています。
VTT files are used to display subtitles for videos.
VTTファイルは動画の字幕を表示するために使われます。
It's a combination of timestamps and text.
タイムスタンプとテキストの組み合わせです。
WebVTT stands for Web Video Text Tracks.
WebVTTはWeb Video Text Tracksの略称です。
It is used for HTML5 video subtitles.
HTML5ビデオの字幕に使用されます。
It can be created in a simple text format.
シンプルなテキスト形式で作成できます。
Each subtitle has a start time and an end time.
各字幕には開始時間と終了時間があります。
Subtitles are displayed in the video player.
字幕はビデオプレーヤーで表示されます。
They help improve accessibility.
アクセシビリティの向上に役立ちます。
They convey content to viewers with hearing impairments.
聴覚障害のある視聴者に内容を伝えます。
They also support understanding of foreign languages.
また、外国語の理解をサポートします。
Subtitles can also be used for translations.
字幕は翻訳にも利用できます。
Content can be understood even in environments where audio cannot be heard.
音声が聞こえない環境でも内容が理解できます。
They also help with search engine optimization.
検索エンジンの最適化にも役立ちます。
This is because they can express video content in text.
動画の内容をテキストで表現できるからです。
Subtitle files can be easily edited.
字幕ファイルは簡単に編集できます。
Just open them in a text editor and make modifications.
テキストエディタで開いて修正するだけです。
The format is very simple.
フォーマットは非常にシンプルです。
It supports various languages.
さまざまな言語に対応しています。
It supports multiple languages including Japanese, English, and Chinese.
日本語、英語、中国語など多言語対応です。
Subtitle styles can also be customized.
字幕のスタイルもカスタマイズできます。
You can change the font, size, color, etc.
フォント、サイズ、色などを変更できます。
Position adjustment is also possible.
位置の調整も可能です。
Subtitles are also effective for educational purposes.
字幕は教育目的にも効果的です。
They are useful for language learning.
語学学習に役立ちます。
You can practice listening and reading comprehension simultaneously.
聞き取りと読解を同時に練習できます。
They are also effective for understanding technical terms.
専門用語の理解にも有効です。
Technical content can be confirmed in text.
技術的な内容をテキストで確認できます。
There are also dedicated tools for creating subtitles.
字幕作成には専用ツールもあります。
Services with automatic generation features are increasing.
自動生成機能を持つサービスも増えています。
Accuracy has improved due to advances in speech recognition technology.
音声認識技術の進歩により精度が向上しています。
Manual correction is still important.
手動での修正は依然として重要です。
Accurate subtitles enhance the viewer experience.
正確な字幕は視聴者体験を向上させます。
Inaccurate subtitles can lead to misunderstandings.
不正確な字幕は誤解を招く可能性があります。
Timing adjustment is also an important task.
タイミングの調整も重要な作業です。
It needs to match the speaker's statements.
話者の発言に合わせる必要があります。
Subtitles also function as metadata for videos.
字幕は動画のメタデータとしても機能します。
They can also be used for chapter or section breaks.
チャプターやセクションの区切りにも使えます。
It is also possible to prepare multiple subtitle tracks.
複数の字幕トラックを用意することも可能です。
You can provide subtitles in different languages and detail levels.
異なる言語や詳細レベルの字幕を提供できます。
It is now possible to add subtitles to live broadcasts.
ライブ配信にも字幕を付けられるようになりました。
Real-time subtitle generation technology is developing.
リアルタイム字幕生成技術が発展しています。
VTT files can be easily integrated into HTML.
VTTファイルはHTMLに簡単に統合できます。
Just specify it with the track tag in the video element.
video要素のtrackタグで指定するだけです。
Subtitles increase the value of video content.
字幕は動画コンテンツの価値を高めます。
You can reach more viewers.
より多くの視聴者にリーチできるようになります。
This VTT file shows 50 subtitle examples.
このVTTファイルは50個の字幕例を示しています。